Guide to George Mason University Faculty Course Evaluations
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- GMU Archives- Faculty/Course Evaluations
  - Music- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Nursing- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Physical Education- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Philosophy- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Physics- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Parks, Recreation and Leisure Studies- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Psychology- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Public Administration- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - PUBP- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Religious Studies- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Russian- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Sociology- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Social Work- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Spanish- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Statistics- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Software Systems Engineering- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Systems Engineering- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Theater- Summer 1994 (Box Box 108)
  - Accounting- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Anthropology- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Arts- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Astronomy- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Biology- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Business Legal Studies- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Chemistry- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Classics- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Communications- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Computer Science- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Computational Sciences and Informatics- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Dance- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Decision Sciences- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Economics- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Community College Education- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Education- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - English- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Finance- Summer 1994 (Box Box 19)
  - French- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Geographic and Cartographic Science- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Geography- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Geology- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - German- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Government- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Health- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - History- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Information Systems- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - International Institute- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Law- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Mathematics- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Management- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Management Information Systems- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Marketing- Summer 1994 (Box Box 107)
  - Management Information Systems- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Mathematics- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Military Sciences- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Music- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Nursing- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Operations Research- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Philosophy- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Parks, Recreation and Leisure Studies- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Psychology- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Physics- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Public Administration- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Public Policy- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Religion- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Russian- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Social Work- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Sociology- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Spanish- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Statistics- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Software Systems Engineering- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Systems Engineering- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Telecommunications- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Theatre- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - University Studies- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Urban Systems Engineering- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Women Studies- Spring 1994 (Box Box 106)
  - Education- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Education Instructional Technology- 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Education Research- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Special Education- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - English- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Engineering- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - French- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Foreign Languages and Literatures- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Geographic and Cartographic Sciences (Box Box 105)
  - Geography- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Geology- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - German- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Government- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Guidance and Counseling- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - History- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Information Technology- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Information Systems- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - International Transactions- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Japanese- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Latin- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Law- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Learning, Program on Social and Organizations- Spring 1994 (Box Box 105)
  - Accounting- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Administration and Supervision- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - African American Studies- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - American Studies- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Anthropology- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Art Institutes- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Art History- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Art Studio- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Astronomy- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Biology- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Business Legal Studies- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Chemistry- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Classics- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Communications- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Community College Education- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Computer Science- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Computational Sciences and Informatics- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Conflict Analysis and Resolution- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Curriculum and Instruction- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Dance- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Decision Sciences- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Doctoral Studies in Education- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Economics- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Finance- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Health- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Managements- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Marketing- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Page- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Physical Education- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Reading- Spring 1994 (Box Box 104)
  - Religion- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Russian- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Social Work- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Sociology- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Spanish- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Statistics- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Software Systems Engineering- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Systems Engineering- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Theatre- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - University Studies- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Urban Systems Engineering- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Urban and Suburban Studies- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Women's Studies- Fall 1993 (Box Box 103)
  - Information Systems- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Information Technology- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - International Transactions- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Japanese- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Latin- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Law School- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Liberal Studies- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - LRNG- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Management- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Management Information Systems- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Marketing- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Math- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Military Science- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Music- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Nursing- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Operations Research- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Page Program- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Philosophy- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Physics- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Physical Education- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Parks, Recreation, and Leisure Studies- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Psychology- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Public Administration- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Public Policy- Fall 1993 (Box Box 102)
  - Curriculum and Instruction- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Education Research- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Reading- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Special Education- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Education- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Education Instructional Technology- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - English- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Engineering- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Exercise Science and Health- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Finance- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - French- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Guidance and Counseling- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Geographic and Cartographic Science- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Geology- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - German- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Government- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Health- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - History- Fall 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Accounting- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Administration and Supervision- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - African American Studies- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - American Studies- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Anthropology- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Art History- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Arts- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Astrology- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Biology- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Business Legal Studies- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Chemistry- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Classics- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Communications- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Conflict Management- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Computer Science- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Computational Science of Informatics- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Decision Sciences- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Doctoral Studies in Education- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Dance- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Economics- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Community College Education- Fall 1993 (Box Box 100)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering (Box Box 100)
  - PRLS- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Psychology- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Public Administration- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Public Policy- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Reading- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Religion- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Russian- Summer 1993 (Box Box 1993)
  - Sociology- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Social Work- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Spanish- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Special Education- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Statistics- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Software Systems Engineering- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Systems Engineering- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Theater- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - VOUE- Summer 1993 (Box Box 99)
  - Accounting- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Administration and Supervision- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Anthropology- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Art History- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Art Studio- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Astronomy- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Biology- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Business Legal Studies- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Chemistry- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Classics- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Communications- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Computer Science- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Computational Sciences and Informatics- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Counseling and Development- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Curriculum and Instruction- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Doctoral Studies in Education- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Dance- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Decision Sciences- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Economics- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Educational Instructional Technology- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Education Research- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Education- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - English- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Finance- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - French- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - FRLN- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Geographic and Cartographic Sciences- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Geography- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Geology- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - German- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Government- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Health- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - History- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Information Systems- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - International Transactions- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Law- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Management- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Management Information Systems- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Marketing- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Mathematics- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Music- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Nursing- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Operations Research- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Physical Education- Summer 1993 (Box Box 1993)
  - Philosophy- Summer 1993 (Box Box 98)
  - Music- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Nursing- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - OP RSCH and APPL STAT- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Page- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - PHED- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - PHIL- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - PRLS- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - PSYC- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - PHYS- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Physics and Astronomy- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Physics- Summer 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Pubp- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Reli- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Russ- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Social and Org. Learning- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Socw- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Soci- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Sociology and Anthropology- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - SPAN- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - STAT- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - SWSE- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - SYST- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - TELE- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - THR- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - UNIV- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - USE- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - WMST- Spring 1993 (Box Box 97)
  - Dance and Theatre- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Decision Sciences- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Economics- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Education- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Elect and Computer ENGR- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - English- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Finance- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Foreign Lang. and Lit. (Box Box 96)
  - Geog and Earth System Sc.- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Health, Sport and LEI ST- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - INFO and SFTWRE AYS ENGR- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Public Affairs- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - History- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Interdisc Studies- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - International Trans.- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Law- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Management- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Marketing- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - International Sciences- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Military Science- Spring 1993 (Box Box 96)
  - Acct. and Bus Legal St.- Spring 1993 (Box Box 95)
  - American Studies- Spring 1993 (Box Box 95)
  - Art and Art History- Spring 1993 (Box Box 95)
  - Biology- Spring 1993 (Box Box 95)
  - Chemistry- Spring 1993 (Box Box 95)
  - Communication- Spring 1993 (Box Box 95)
  - Comp Sci and Informatics- Spring 1993 (Box Box 95)
  - Computer Sciences- Spring 1993 (Box Box 95)
  - Conflict Resolution- Spring 1993 (Box Box 95)
  - Contract Course- Spring 1993 (Box Box 95)
  - Public Policy- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Physics- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Religion- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Russian- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Social Work- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Sociology- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Software Systems Engineering- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Spanish- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Statistics- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Systems Engineering- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Theater- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - University Courses- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Urban and Suburban Studies- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Urban Systems Engineering- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Women's Studies- Fall 1992 (Box Box 94)
  - Music- Fall 1992 (Box Box 93)
  - Nursing- Fall 1992 (Box Box 93)
  - Operations Research- Fall 1992 (Box Box 93)
  - Page- Fall 1992 (Box Box 93)
  - Philosophy- Fall 1992 (Box Box 93)
  - Psychology- Fall 1992 (Box Box 93)
  - Public Administration- Fall 1992 (Box Box 93)
  - Information Systems- Fall 1992 (Box Box 92)
  - Information Technology- Fall 1992 (Box Box 92)
  - International Transactions- Fall 1992 (Box Box 92)
  - Japanese- Fall 1992 (Box Box 92)
  - Latin- Fall 1992 (Box Box 92)
  - Law- Fall 1992 (Box Box 92)
  - Management- Fall 1992 (Box Box 92)
  - Management Information Systems- Fall 1992 (Box Box 92)
  - Marketing- Fall 1992 (Box Box 92)
  - Mathematics- Fall 1992 (Box Box 92)
  - Military Science- Fall 1992 (Box Box 92)
  - English- Fall 1992 (Box Box 91)
  - European Studies- Fall 1992 (Box Box 91)
  - Finance- Fall 1992 (Box Box 91)
  - Foreign Languages- fall 1992 (Box Box 91)
  - French- Fall 1992 (Box Box 91)
  - Geographic and Cartographic Sciences- Fall 1992 (Box Box 91)
  - Geography- Fall 1992 (Box Box 91)
  - Geology- Fall 1992 (Box Box 91)
  - German- Fall 1992 (Box Box 91)
  - Government- Fall 1992 (Box Box 91)
  - Health, Sports and Leisure Studies (Box Box 91)
  - History- Fall 1992 (Box Box 91)
  - Computer Science- Fall 1992 (Box Box 90)
  - Conflict Management- Fall 1992 (Box Box 90)
  - Contract Courses- Fall 1992 (Box Box 90)
  - Core- Fall 1992 (Box Box 90)
  - Dance- Fall 1992 (Box Box 90)
  - Decision Sciences- Fall 1992 (Box Box 90)
  - Economics- Fall 1992 (Box Box 90)
  - Education- Fall 1992 (Box Box 90)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Fall 1992 (Box Box 90)
  - Engineering- Fall 1992 (Box Box 90)
  - English- Fall 1992 (Box Box 90)
  - Accounting/Bule- Fall 1992 (Box Box 89)
  - American Studies- Fall 1992 (Box Box 89)
  - Anthropology- Fall 1992 (Box Box 89)
  - Art/Art History- Fall 1992 (Box Box 89)
  - Arts Institute- Fall 1992 (Box Box 89)
  - Astronomy- Fall 1992 (Box Box 1992)
  - Biology- Fall 1992 (Box Box 89)
  - Biology (Cluster Core)- Fall 1992 (Box Box 89)
  - Chemistry- Fall 1992 (Box Box 89)
  - Classics- Fall 1992 (Box Box 89)
  - Communication- Fall 1992 (Box Box 89)
  - Computational Sciences and Informatics- Fall 1992 (Box Box 89)
  - Page- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Parks, Recreation- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Philosophy- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Psychology- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Public Administration- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Physics- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Religion- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Russian- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Social Work- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Sociology- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Software System Engineering- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Spanish- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Statistics- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Systems Engineering- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Systems Technology- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Theatre- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - University- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Urban and Suburban Studies- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Women's Studies- Spring 1992 (Box Box 88)
  - Information Technology- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - International Relations- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - History- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - Japanese- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - Latin- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - Law- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - Management- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - Marketing- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - Masters in Individualized Studies- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - Math- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - Military Science- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - Music- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - Nursing- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - Operations Research- Spring 1992 (Box Box 87)
  - English- Spring 1992 (Box Box 86)
  - Finance- Spring 1992 (Box Box 86)
  - Foreign Language- Spring 1992 (Box Box 86)
  - French- Spring 1992 (Box Box 86)
  - Geography- Spring 1992 (Box Box 86)
  - Geo. and Carto. Sciences- Spring 1992 (Box Box 86)
  - Geology- Spring 1992 (Box Box 86)
  - German- Spring 1992 (Box Box 86)
  - Government- Spring 1992 (Box Box 86)
  - Communication- Spring 1992 (Box Box 85)
  - Computer Science- Spring 1992 (Box Box 85)
  - Conflict Management- Spring 1992 (Box Box 85)
  - Contract Course- Spring 1992 (Box Box 85)
  - Dance- Spring 1992 (Box Box 85)
  - Decision Sciences- Spring 1992 (Box Box 85)
  - Economics- Spring 1992 (Box Box 85)
  - Education- Spring 1992 (Box Box 85)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Spring 1992 (Box Box 85)
  - Accounting/Bule- Spring 1992 (Box Box 84)
  - American Studies- Spring 1992 (Box Box 84)
  - Anthropology- Spring 1992 (Box Box 84)
  - Art- Spring 1992 (Box Box 84)
  - Astronomy- Spring 1992 (Box Box 84)
  - Biology- Spring 1992 (Box Box 84)
  - Chemistry- Spring 1992 (Box Box 84)
  - Biology- Spring 1992 (Box Box 84)
  - Classics- Spring 1992 (Box Box 84)
  - Psychology- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Public Administration- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Physics- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Religion- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Russian- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Social Work- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Sociology- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Spanish- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Statistics- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Systems Technology- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Theater- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - University- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Urban Systems Engineering- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Women's Studies- Fall 1991 (Box Box 83)
  - Mathematics- Fall 1991 (Box Box 82)
  - Management- Fall 1991 (Box Box 82)
  - Marketing- Fall 1991 (Box Box 82)
  - Military Science- Fall 1991 (Box Box 82)
  - MIS- Fall 1991 (Box Box 82)
  - Music- Fall 1991 (Box Box 82)
  - Nursing- Fall 1991 (Box Box 82)
  - Operations Research- Fall 1991 (Box Box 82)
  - PAGE- Fall 1991 (Box Box 82)
  - Parks, Recreation and Leisure Studies (Box Box 82)
  - Philosophy- Fall 1991 (Box Box 82)
  - Physical Education- Fall 1991 (Box Box 82)
  - Geology- Fall 1991 (Box Box 81)
  - Government- Fall 1991 (Box Box 81)
  - Health- Fall 1991 (Box Box 81)
  - History- Fall 1991 (Box Box 81)
  - Information Systems- Fall 1991 (Box Box 81)
  - Information Technology- Fall 1991 (Box Box 81)
  - International Institute- Fall 1991 (Box Box 81)
  - Japanese- Fall 1991 (Box Box 81)
  - Latin- Fall 1991 (Box Box 81)
  - Law- Fall 1991 (Box Box 81)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Fall 1991 (Box Box 80)
  - Engineering- Fall 1991 (Box Box 80)
  - English- Fall 1991 (Box Box 80)
  - European Studies- Fall 1991 (Box Box 80)
  - Finance- Fall 1991 (Box Box 80)
  - Foreign Language- Fall 1991 (Box Box 80)
  - French- Fall 1991 (Box Box 1991)
  - Geographic and Cartographic Sciences- Fall 1991 (Box Box 80)
  - German- Fall 1991 (Box Box 80)
  - Communications- Fall 1991 (Box Box 79)
  - Computer Science- Fall 1991 (Box Box 79)
  - Conflict Resolution- Fall 1991 (Box Box 79)
  - CORE- Fall 1991 (Box Box 79)
  - Dance- Fall 1991 (Box Box 79)
  - Des. Science- Fall 1991 (Box Box 79)
  - Economics- Fall 1991 (Box Box 79)
  - Education- Fall 1991 (Box Box 79)
  - Accounting- Fall 1991 (Box Box 78)
  - American Studies- Fall 1991 (Box Box 78)
  - Anthropology- Fall 1991 (Box Box 78)
  - Art- Fall 1991 (Box Box 78)
  - Astronomy- Fall 1991 (Folder Box 78)
  - Biology- Fall 1991 (Box Box 78)
  - Business Legal Studies- Fall 1991 (Box Box 78)
  - Master's in Business Administration- Fall 1991 (Box Box 78)
  - Chemistry- Fall 1991 (Box Box 78)
  - Classics- Fall 1991 (Box Box 78)
  - Physics- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - PRLS-Parks, Recreation, and Leisure Studies- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - Psychology- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - Public Administration- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - ROTC- Military Science- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - Russian- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - Social Work- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - SWSE- Software Systems Engineering- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - Sociology- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - Spanish- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - Statistics- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - SYST- Systems Engineering- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - Telecommunications- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - Theater- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - University Course- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - USE- Urban Systems Engineering- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - USST- Urban and Suburban Studies- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - Women's Studies- Spring 1991 (Box Box 77)
  - Accounting- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - American Studies- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - Anthropology- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - Art History- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)